<resources>
    <string name="app_name">eTeachSwayam</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="video_title">Title</string>

    <string name="notification_catalog_downloaded">Downloading Please Wait </string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="navigation_item_1">Home</string>
    <string name="navigation_item_2">Events</string>
    <string name="starred_string">Starred</string>
    <string name="my_profile">My Profile</string>
    <string name="activate_now">Activate Now</string>
    <string name="storage">Storage</string>
    <string name="transfer_content">Transfer Content</string>
    <string name="updates">Updates</string>
    <string name="feedbacks">Feedbacks</string>
    <string name="terms_conditions">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="supports">Supports</string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="helps">Help</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="closeDrawer">Navigation View</string>
    <string name="openDrawer">Navigation View Closed</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string-array name="array_board">
        <item>CBSE</item>
        <item>ICSE</item>
        <item>STATE</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="arry_medium">
        <item>English</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="arry_class">
        <item>Class I</item>
        <item>Class II</item>
        <item>Class III</item>
        <item>Class IV</item>
        <item>Class V</item>
        <item>Class VI</item>
        <item>Class VII</item>
        <item>Class VIII</item>
        <item>Class IX</item>
        <item>Class X</item>
        <item>Class XI</item>
        <item>Class XII</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="arry_subject">
        <item>SCIENCE</item>
        <item>MATHS</item>
        <item>GK</item>
        <item>SOCIAL STUDIES</item>
        <item>COMPUTER</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email Id</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="log_in">Log In</string>
    <string name="btnRegister">Register</string>
    <string name="title_activity_register">RegisterActivity</string>



    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email1">User Id</string>
    <string name="prompt_password1">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_register"><b>Sign in</b></string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="menu_forgot_password">Recover lost password</string>
    <string name="login_progress_signing_in">Signing in....</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">password must contain at least 6 characters</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="des">Add New User</string>

    <string name="eteach_term_condition">eTeach Terms of Service

Last modified: May 2, 2013

Welcome to eTeach!

Thanks for using our products and services (referred as “Services” hereafter). The Services are
provided by Designo Media Works India Private Limited (“eTeach”), a company registered and
incorporated under the provisions of the Companies Act, 1956, and having its registered office at 202,
2nd Floor, Ameya Towers, Adjacent Dinanath High School, Humpyard Road, Dhantoli, Nagpur – 440012,
Maharashtra. eTeach is the registered trademark of Designo Media Works India Private Limited.

By using our Services, you are agreeing to these terms. Please read them carefully.

Our Services are very diverse, so sometimes additional terms or product requirements may apply.
Additional terms will be available with the relevant Services, and those additional terms become part of
your agreement with us if you use those Services.

Using our Services

You must follow any policies made available to you within the Services.

Don’t misuse our Services. For example, don’t interfere with our Services or try to access them using a
method other than the interface and the instructions that we provide. You may use our Services only
as permitted by law, including applicable export and re-export control laws and regulations. We may
suspend or stop providing our Services to you if you do not comply with our terms or policies or if we
are investigating suspected misconduct.

Using our Services does not give you ownership of any intellectual property rights in our Services or the
content you access. You may not use content from our Services unless you obtain permission from its
owner or are otherwise permitted by law. These terms do not grant you the right to use any branding or
logos used in our Services. Don’t remove, obscure, or alter any legal notices displayed in or along with
our Services.

Our Services display some content that is not eTeach’s. This content is the sole responsibility of the
entity that makes it available. We may review content to determine whether it is illegal or violates
our policies, and we may remove or refuse to display content that we reasonably believe violates our
policies or the law. But that does not necessarily mean that we review content, so please don’t assume
that we do.

In connection with your use of the Services, we may send you service announcements, administrative
messages, and other information. You may opt out of some of those communications.

Your eTeach Account

You may need an eTeach Account in order to use some of our Services. You may create your own
eTeach Account by buying an eTeach Service, or your eTeach Account may be assigned to you
by an administrator, such as your educational institution. The license or Account purchased for using
eTeach Services would be valid for a pre-specified period of time. If you are using an eTeach TM
Account assigned to you by an administrator, different or additional terms may apply and your
administrator may be able to access or disable your account.
If you learn of any unauthorized use of your password or account, immediately contact your
administrator or customer care.

Privacy and Copyright Protection

eTeach’s privacy policies explain how we treat your personal data and protect your privacy when you
use our Services. By using our Services, you agree that eTeach can use such data in accordance with
our privacy policies.

Entire eTeach has been protected under Indian copyright laws and we respond to notices of alleged
copyright infringement and might take legal action against infringers according to the process set out by
Indian laws.

If you think somebody is violating our copyrights and want to notify us, you can provide the information
to your administrator or customer care.

Your Content in our Services

Some of our Services might allow you to submit content or data. You retain ownership of any
intellectual property rights that you hold in that content. In short, what belongs to you stays yours.

When you upload or otherwise submit content or data to our Services, you give eTeach TM (and those
we work with) a worldwide license to use, host, store, reproduce, modify, create derivative works (such
as those resulting from translations, adaptations or other changes we make so that your content works
better with our Services), communicate, publish, publicly perform, publicly display and distribute such
content. The rights you grant in this license are for the limited purpose of operating, promoting, and
improving our Services, and to develop new ones. This license continues even if you stop using our
Services. Some Services may offer you ways to access and remove content that has been provided to
that Service. Also, in some of our Services, there are terms or settings that narrow the scope of our use
of the content submitted in those Services. Make sure you have the necessary rights to grant us this
license for any content that you submit to our Services.

If you submit feedback or suggestions about our Services, we may use your feedback or suggestions
without obligation to you.

About Software in our Services

When a Service requires or includes downloadable software, this software may update automatically on
your device once a new version or feature is available. Some Services may let you adjust your automatic
update settings.

eTeach gives you a personal, worldwide, non-assignable and non-exclusive license to use the software
provided to you by eTeach as part of the Services. This license is for the sole purpose of enabling you
to use and enjoy the benefit of the Services as provided by eTeach, in the manner permitted by these
terms. You may not copy, modify, distribute, sell, or lease any part of our Services or included software,
nor may you reverse engineer or attempt to extract the source code of that software, unless you have
our written permission.

Modifying and Terminating our Services

We are constantly changing and improving our Services. We may add or remove functionalities or
features, and we may suspend or stop a Service altogether.

You can stop using our Services at any time, including the time for which Service license is purchased
but software not already installed, though the money paid against purchase of such license won’t
be refunded. However, you may contact customer care and request for a refund under special
circumstances. The decision to make a refund lies solely at discretion of eTeach TM. eTeach may also
stop providing Services to you, or add or create new limits to our Services at any time.

We believe that you own your data and preserving your access to such data is important. If we
discontinue a Service, where reasonably possible, we will give you reasonable advance notice and a
chance to get information out of that Service.

Our Warranties and Disclaimers

We provide our Services using a commercially reasonable level of skill and care and we hope that you
will enjoy using them. But there are certain things that we don’t promise about our Services.

Other than as expressly set out in these terms or additional terms, neither eTeach TM nor its suppliers
or distributors make any specific promises about the Services. For example, we don’t make any
commitments about the content within the Services, the specific functions of the Services, or their
reliability, availability, accuracy, quality or ability to meet your needs. We provide the Services “as is”.

Some jurisdictions provide for certain warranties, like the implied warranty of merchantability,
fitness for a particular purpose and non-infringement. To the extent permitted by law, we exclude all
warranties.

Liability for our Services

When permitted by law eTeach, and eTeach’s suppliers and distributors, will not be responsible for
lost profits, revenues, or data, financial losses or indirect, special, consequential, exemplary, or punitive
damages.

To the extent permitted by law, the total liability of eTeach, and its suppliers and distributors, for any
claims under these terms, including for any implied warranties, is limited to the amount you paid us to
use the Services (or, if we choose, to supplying you the Services again).

In all cases, eTeach, and its suppliers and distributors, will not be liable for any loss or damage that is
not reasonably foreseeable.

Business uses of our Services

If you are using our Services on behalf of a business, that business accepts these terms. It will hold
harmless and indemnify eTeach and its affiliates, officers, agents, and employees from any claim, suit
or action arising from or related to the use of the Services or violation of these terms, including any
liability or expense arising from claims, losses, damages, suits, judgments, litigation costs and attorneys’
fees.

About these Terms

We may modify these terms or any additional terms that apply to a Service to, for example, reflect
changes to the law or changes to our Services. You should look at the terms regularly. We’ll post

notice of modifications to these terms on our website www.eteach.co.in. We’ll post notice of modified
additional terms in the applicable Service, if internet connection is available at client’s end. Changes
will not apply retroactively and will become effective no sooner than seven days after they are posted.
However, changes addressing new functions for a Service or changes made for legal reasons will be
effective immediately. If you do not agree to the modified terms for a Service, you should discontinue
your use of that Service.

If there is a conflict between these terms and the additional terms issued by Designo Media Works India
Private Limited, the additional terms will control for that conflict.

These terms control the relationship between eTeach and you. They do not create any third party
beneficiary rights.

If you do not comply with these terms, and we don’t take action right away, this doesn’t mean that we
are giving up any rights that we may have (such as taking action in the future).

If it turns out that a particular term is not enforceable, this will not affect any other terms.

The courts in some countries will not apply Indian laws to some types of disputes. If you reside in one
of those countries, then where Indian laws are excluded from applying, your country’s laws will apply
to such disputes related to these terms. Otherwise, you agree that the laws of India, will apply to any
disputes arising out of or relating to these terms or the Services. Jurisdiction of any disputes related to
these terms would be settled in city of Nagpur, Maharashtra, India only.

For information about how to contact eTeach, please visit our website www.eteach.co.in.</string>
</resources>
